MADHUMITHA SHREE D

PRODUCT DESIGNER

EDUCATION

M.S.RAMAIAH UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES

Bachelor In Product Designing (B.Des)

Banglore,Karnataka 2018-2022

SRI VIDYAMANDIR HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL

Higher Secondary Education

Krishnagiri,Tamilnadu

2016-2018

HOLY ANGELS' MATRICULATION SCHOOL

Secondary Education Salem, Tamilnadu 2010-2015

NOTRE DAME OF HOLY CROSS PUBLIC SCHOOL

Primay Education Salem,Tamilnadu 2005-2010

LANGUAGES KNOWN

| ENGLISH | TAMIL | HINDI |
|---------|-------|-------|
| R S W | R S W | R - W |

HOBBY

Classical Dance

Chess

Painting

Comic Illustrations

Reading and Listening Fairy Tales

STRENGTHS

Critical Thinking Poblem Solving On-Time Doer Adaptive Organizational Skills Stress Tolerance Loyalty

PORTFOLIO LINKS

Behance

https://www.behance.net/madhu288202e59

Issuu

https://issuu.com/madhum_i_t_h_a_d?





madhu28820@gmail.com



6379852517



Madhumitha Shree

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Hello, I'm a 21 year old Industrial Designer from Banglore, India. I have always been fascinated by trends and good design. All my skills have been self learnt with inspiration from a lot of famous and my favorite designers which made me inquisite and most importantly a better designer by quality of empathy

2D SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Adobe Indesign Adobe XD Autodesk Sketchbook Pro Figma

3D SKILLS

Sketch Up Autodesk Alias Keyshot Catia V5 Blender Revit Architecture

PROJECTS

Design and Development of Aquaponics System

4 Months (2021)

Designed and developed a smart aquaponics system which consumes less space for urban and residential places.

Design and Development of Handicraft Toys that represent tradition

4 Months (2021)

Designed and developed a kitchen set toy for girls representing old tradition in a modernistic way.

Design and Development of Smart Wearable Badge

1 Months (2021)

Designed and developed a smart wearable device that detects sleep health for IT professionals

Design and Development of Space saving furntiures

4 Months (2020)

Designed and developed a convertible table that turns into sofa, bed for people living in apartments and small houses

EXPERIENCE

Kaafila under CCX News

Product Designer | UI UX Designer | Graphic Designer April 2021 - Present

Warpe Edutech Company

Graphic Designer

April 2021-September 2021

Together Commerce

Freelance Graphic and UI Designer September 2021 | February 2022

NAF Organisation

Graphic Designer

January 2021 - April 2021